<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<description>
	<welcometext>
		Welcome to the KeYmaera tutorial overview...
	</welcometext>
	<tutorials>
		<tutorial name="Verified Software Summer School 2012">
			<description>
				This tutorial contains the exercises used at the Verified Software Summer School 2012.
			</description>
			<exercise>
				<title>Ex. 1 Pen&amp;Paper Modelling</title>
				<description>Use Pen&amp;Paper to model a car.</description>
			</exercise>
			<exercise>
				<title>Ex. 2 Dynamics</title>
				<description>Given the following system of...</description>
				<path>/examples/hybrid/tutorial/lics1-continuous-forward.key</path>
			</exercise>
			<exercise>
				<title>Ex. 3 Water Tank</title>
				<description>
				<![CDATA[
					<p>
					The given input file models a water tank. The water level (named y) is supposed to be between 1 and 12. Another variable x is used as clock to model delays while switching modes.
					</p>

					<p>
					The system has two main modes:
					<ul>
					<li> st = 0: is the mode where water is flowing into the tank with a constant rate of 1.</li>
					<li> st = 2: is the mode where water is draining from the tank with a constant rate of -2.</li>
					</ul>
					</p>
					<p>
					The modes st = 1 and st = 3 model the delays while switching between modes 0 and 2.
					</p>
					<p>
					<b>Exercise:</b> Load the example and press play. The automatic strategy is able to proof this example using the annotated loop invariant in the input file. 
					</p>
				
				]]>
					
				</description>
			    <img href="http://symbolaris.com/info/fig-water-tank.png"/>
			    <path>/examples/hybrid/publish/water_tank.key</path>
			</exercise>
			<exercise>
				<title>Ex. 4 Parametric Water Tank</title>
				<description>
					<![CDATA[
					<p>
					The given input file again models a water tank. Now, the water level (named y) is supposed to be between min_fill and max_fill. Another variable x is used as clock to model delays while switching modes. The delay is bounded by a constant max_com.
					</p>

					<p>
						The system has two main modes (for f > 0 & d > 0):
					<ul>
						<li> st = 0: is the mode where water is flowing into the tank with a constant rate of <b>f</b>.</li>
						<li> st = 2: is the mode where water is draining from the tank with a constant rate of <b>-d</b>.</li>
					</ul>
					</p>
					<p>
					The modes st = 1 and st = 3 model the delays while switching between modes 0 and 2.
					</p>
					<p>
					<b>Exercise:</b> Load the example. And proof that the input is a tautology. Note that in contrast to the previous exercise the loop invariant is not given.
					</p>
				]]>
				</description>
			    <img href="http://symbolaris.com/info/fig-water-tank.png"/>
				 <path>/examples/hybrid/verifiedsoft/general_water_tank.key</path>
			</exercise>
		</tutorial>
	</tutorials>
</description>
